(Wherever You Are)
(The talk of the town last week)
(Moo chewy cookies)
("Jun Hyun Moo's Moo Chewy Cookies Tops the Ratings")
("Moo Chewy Cookies Taste as Shocking as They Look")
(To stabilize the supply of DCC,)
(Moomoo was deployed.)
(Let's start from scratch.)
(From shelling pistachios...)
(to making his own kadayif,)
(he made Moo chewy cookies from scratch.)
(I screamed when I saw the pistachios fall.)
(Come on, you've got to be kidding me. It's so stressful.)
(Getting a headache)
(I decided to make DCC and ought to see it through.)
(A huge chewy cookie)
(Here are Dubai-style pancakes.)
(Despite how it looks, it tastes authentic.)
(Thick and moist)
(Do you want it?)
(After wrapping them in hip packaging, he headed...)
(Moomoo's After-Sales Service)
(Out of gratitude,)
(he decided to provide after-sales service.)
(Utterly satisfied)
(The next spot, Moomoo's dream spot)
(Hue's house)
(People line up to buy that.)
(I bought it for you.)
(That's for me?)
(He gave Hue keyboard pedals.)
(You're like Santa Claus.)
(I'm loving myself right now.)
(Moo chewy cookies for the members)
(Can you give me three more?)
(Moo chewy cookies were a hit too.)
(He headed to Jae Hyeon's house next.)
(I'm here.)
(Winking)
(My intercom doesn't have a screen.)
(Making a scene)
(Hyun Moo arrives in the parking lot of Jae Hyeon's building.)
(Struggling)
Hyun Moo.
(The third member shows up with a smile.)
The third spot of Moomoo's After-Sales Service is...
the new owner of the oven, Jae Hyeon's house.
(At the last bazaar,)
(Hyun Moo's oven was a headache.)
(Who's going to buy that?)
(But Jae Hyeon was the only one who showed interest.)
(The listed price is between 3,500 to 4,500 dollars.)
(But I'll sell it to you for 1,000 dollars.)
(We have a deal!)
(He gladly bought it for his friends who were planning to open a cafe.)
That was the most expensive item at the bazaar that day.
- Right. - Yes.
(The oven will finally meet its owner.)
I can't believe the oven got a new owner.
- This is... - Wait.
- Hyun Moo, grab the bottom. - Wait.
One, two, three. Just like this. We got it.
- Do I need all of them? - They're all yours.
- Really? - Yes. I'm giving them to you.
- There are stones too. - Okay.
- You need them. - When do you need them?
For baking.
The oven rack looks really good too.
- It's... - He got it custom-made.
- I did. Yes. - Really?
Hyun Moo. Someone finally recognizes its value...
- after it got sold. - Exactly.
You can move another oven to his house then.
I'll help you.
- Do I have to be... - You must transport it.
responsible for its final transport too?
It's like life insurance.
- You have to help him sell it. - I'm selling life insurance.
- Finally. - Hyun Moo, wait.
What?
- What? - There are stairs to the elevator.
- What? - What?
It doesn't directly lead to the elevator.
No. We have to walk up the stairs.
- Right. - That's bad.
- Install the oven here. - No. We can get going.
- We can do this. - Hey, this...
- Should we push them like this? - Yes, let's go.
But there must be only a few stairs, not that many.
- But the oven was quite heavy. - But it was still pretty tough.
- Just watch. - Right, the oven is really heavy.
Hold on.
- The door is open. - Just install it here.
Hold on. Let me keep the door open.
My gosh. No.
- I can't do it. - What's wrong?
(Behind the entrance door, there are...)
- See? - No way.
People often assume that they can use the elevator...
- directly from the parking lot. - Right.
- That's right. - Who would have thought...
- there would be stairs? - Right.
You'll have to move it to Bum June's house anyway.
The two of you...
Hyun Moo will move it for you.
- Hold on. We should... - Wait.
I'll lift it from here.
All right. One, two, three.
(Struggling)
We got it.
(It's even difficult to lift it over the threshold.)
- Hold on. This... My gosh. - We must carry them separately.
- Not at once, right? - What?
- Should we carry them at once? - At once?
No, right?
- I think we can do it. - What?
- Let's do it in one go. - Yes. I think we can do it.
- You can support me from the back. - It might be possible...
- since there are two of them. - Exactly.
It must be possible.
(Strong thighs)
Right. He's got strong thighs.
(Massive arm muscles)
(I'm a strong man, Ahn Jae Hyeon.)
- You look great. - You're a real man.
- A real man. - You're Thor.
- You've been working out, right? - Of course.
- Wait. But I can't see ahead. - Okay.
Wait.
(Wait.)
- Is it going up? - Yes, you're doing a good job.
Hyun Moo, wait.
(They stop only after going up one step.)
Keep going.
No, don't!
(A shocking fall of Thor?)
- Both of you are awful at this. - That's so true.
- We should've separated them. - You should've separated them.
- You've never done manual work. - Seriously.
- Right. Look at his fair skin. - We wanted to do it in one go.
When I tried to lift it up, the oven rack hit my shins.
- Right. Look how tall it is. - That's why?
- You can't move them in one go. - No way.
- My gosh. - That's not possible, right?
It kept hitting my shins too.
I somehow hurt my arm that day. It's still bruised.
- My goodness. - It got bruised that day.
My gosh.
I thought you were getting an electric shock.
(It's expected of Thor.)
Keep going. No, don't!
(Lightning)
- Put it down. - Let's put it down.
- Is this too much for you? - It's...
No, it's not. But can you go up?
- It's hard because of the incline. - Are you serious?
It's harder for the guy in the back.
Wait.
(What do we do with this?)
Then let's carry it up sideways.
- How? - Let's go horizontal.
- There's not enough space. - Really?
Or should we carry it up diagonally?
Wait.
- Do you have enough space? - Can you go up?
We can't.
(Giving up quickly)
(Struggling)
- You should move them separately. - No.
Jae Hyeon is really weak.
It was a tough day.
There was a time...
Jae Hyeon was really fit.
It could've worked if he was still fit.
But he went back to his old days.
Muscles are so merciless.
- They're gone without any exercise. - Exactly.
Let's carry them one at a time.
- One at a time? - Let's move the oven first.
- The oven first? - Yes.
- Should I carry this first? - There's no way around it.
- Can you lift it? One, two. - I can.
- I got this. - We should've done this first.
- That's true. - Hey, we could've done this first.
Right. You can move it one at a time.
- We could've done it first. - I see.
Obviously. Why would you want to carry the rack with it?
It was so much easier then.
You guys are so clueless.
(Sighing)
(Grunting)
- I'll get the rack. I can do it. - No.
This is light.
Then try moving it on your own.
- This is good. I can do it. - You're good.
- Then you can move the rack. - That's light.
Right.
We should've done that from the start.
(We should've done that from the start.)
- One, two, three. - Two...
That's good.
- That's easy. - All right.
- All done. - Okay.
We got it.
- Did we align them well? Yes. - Yes.
Well done.
(Exhausted)
If your building didn't have an elevator...
No way.
I would've given up, right?
One. Okay.
I can't believe I'm going to your house.
- This is your first time, right? - Yes.
Hold on. Can it fit through? There's another door inside.
Another door?
What a headache.
- Wait. Can it fit through the side? - Another door?
- Should we even try? - Should we?
- Wait. I think it will fit through. - My gosh, no.
Here it goes.
(Let's try pushing it in.)
- I got it. - It can fit through?
- No way. - It won't.
One, two, three.
(Lifting)
It's stuck.
- Right. It can't fit through. - It won't.
- We have to remove the door. - Can you do it?
(It's so hard to bring it into the house.)
- Seriously. - I was so stressed by that point.
(Rattling)
You can do it right away.
I saw the workers remove it once.
But I didn't see them putting it back.
- Putting it back... - That should be easy.
- Let's do it. - One, two.
Three.
(They finally bring the oven inside the house.)
Hey. Okay. I got it.
(Exhausted)
It's like watching "Pat and Mat."
Gosh, I'm sweating.
Why are you sweating so much?
What's wrong with you? You're out of shape now?
- Where should I put this? - Where... I haven't decided yet.
You're not going to use this, right?
- Will you? - I doubt it.
- No. It's for your friend, right? - Yes.
It's better to shove it inside a room you don't use.
Really?
Let me give you a tour of the house.
(Unused space in the house...)
- All right. - My gosh.
- What's this? Why do you have this? - This is my bedroom.
- My gosh. How cute. - Goodness.
- Is it Anju? - Is Anju friendly?
- Anju. It's been a while. - Look at you.
Anju doesn't bite.
- Look at you. - Anju.
- How cute. - He's so cute.
He looks like a marshmallow.
- Do you want to hold him? - Yes.
Like this.
- Anju. - Right.
- Anju. - How is it? Is he heavy?
Anju. He's not heavy.
- Right. He's slim. - Anju.
He's not moving at all.
He looks like a white DCC.
I love him.
I keep my clothes in this room.
- I don't think I can put it here. - Anju.
The oven is quite big.
The oven was much bigger than I thought.
- Since you're here... - Yes.
There are some clothes I can't wear because they're small.
What do you think? Take a look at this.
It's the last piece of clothing from Givenchy I own.
It's good, right?
It's too tight on me. So I can't wear it.
He suddenly lit up.
I saved it for special occasions.
(Let me try it on.)
(My gosh, it's Givenchy!)
- Because you bulked up? - Yes, so it's too tight on me.
You can't throw out some clothes because they're from luxury brands.
- This is good. - Do you like it?
- My gosh. - Does it fit you?
Yes. It looks so good on me. Gosh.
This is perfect for me.
Doesn't it look great on me?
(This is mine.)
What do you think? Will you wear it or not?
- I will. Yes. - It's a good jacket, right?
- You can't take it back. - The jacket is layered. Look.
- Forget it. It's Givenchy. - The jacket... Really?
I'll give you the clothes hanger for it too.
Yes. Thank you.
Here you go. It feels good to have proper clothes hangers.
The clothes hanger from Givenchy.
- I don't own one from Givenchy. - Really?
- You don't have one from Givenchy? - No, I don't.
That's good then.
- I'll hang it here for now. - Okay.
You'll take it home.
Why am I smelling curry?
I made curry.
- Why is everyone trying to feed me? - He's going to eat again?
Let me take a look at this.
I thought about placing this...
- where my bicycle is. - Yes, that's a good spot too.
It's your oven now. So don't ask me.
The house...
But when people come over, they will think that...
- you're serious about cooking. - Really?
- When you bake bread with it, - Yes.
- your house will smell like bread. - Really?
- It's no joke? - The buttery smell...
This looks like a nice spot.
I can get an extension cord.
- Right. - There's a window here.
Right. It creates a lot of heat at the back.
So it's better if it's open in the back.
- I like it here for now. - Yes.
- It's still in the same spot. - It is?
- You can't put it anywhere else. - It's still there.
So I move it and then put it back.
There are trendy DCC from Seongsu. Do you know about them?
- Yes. - Have you tried them?
- Were you able to buy them? - No.
Have you had DCC?
I have.
- I have. - But from a legit place?
No, I don't think I had authentic ones.
Do you know a good place for it?
- Yes. - Where is it?
- I bought some. - What?
- I bought some. - You did?
Yes. Sit down.
You'll go crazy once you look at them.
He will.
- He will go crazy for sure. - I really thought he bought them.
- I waited in line for a long time. - Really?
I waited for 4 hours, but I could only buy 2.
- Gosh, this is crazy. - Where did you buy them?
In the basement food court of the department store.
A high-end brand was doing a pop-up event there.
- This is crazy, right? - That sounds convincing.
Each cookie cost 40 dollars.
- It cost 40 dollars? - I could only buy 2.
And I bought the last two.
(Falling for the lie)
- I can't wait to try it. - It looks so good too.
- I want to try it. - I could picture him buying them.
- That's understandable. - Seriously.
He would've bought them...
- even if they cost 400 dollars. - Right.
- As long as they're trendy. - As long as they're trendy.
As long as they're trendy.
- Let's have this after curry. - Let's have some curry.
- I saw you... - Yes.
having curry in the waiting room.
So I made curry.
He's so thoughtful.
Where should I sit? There?
Wherever you want.
Let's eat it on the sofa.
- Should we? - Yes.
Let's see how good Jae Hyeon's curry tastes.
My gosh. It's very good.
Anju.
(Looking indifferent)
(Poking)
You don't like that.
(Adorable)
Come at me.
(Meowing)
(Kitty punches)
My gosh. You're upset now?
It's ready.
- Gosh, that looks good. - That looks great.
Homemade curry.
I only added meat and potatoes.
Adding a lot of meat and potatoes is an adult privilege...
- That's right. No carrots. - since we can make it ourselves.
- The scallion kimchi. - You know.
(A plate of scallion kimchi to eat with curry)
The scallion kimchi looks amazing.
What do you think? It's got a nice color, right?
(A curry meal for President Jun who came for the post-sales service)
- Thank you for the meal. - Enjoy.
I hope you like it.
(Taking a big spoonful of the curry)
What do you think? Is it good?
Moving the oven was a tough job. Please eat a lot.
(He eats it with the scallion kimchi this time.)
(Look at this guy.)
Isn't the scallion kimchi really good?
The scallion kimchi.
- That's so good. - Gosh, it looks so tasty.
I'm so hungry.
The pork is really tender.
- It melts in your mouth. Good. - Yes.
I made it yesterday on purpose.
It's better the day after.
You made it tenderer...
- by cooking it the day before? - Yes.
You know it's better the day after, right?
- It was so good. - That's so true.
Of course.
My gosh, that looks so good.
It's been a while since I had curry.
- Same here. - Yes.
(Shockingly, he had ramyeon and a plate of sushi before this.)
He ate so much that day.
He seemed to enjoy it.
His curry is good.
(Approving it as good curry)
My gosh, you're good at cooking.
Hey, it's so good?
Did you finish it?
Dubai chewy cookies?
In the basement food court... My gosh, seriously.
I've never waited in line for four hours for some cookies.
(Rummaging through)
Should I bring a cute plate?
- You should. They're so fancy. - Right.
He's really looking forward to it.
I really did.
The people behind me got so angry.
- Because you were the last one? - "Then why did I wait in line?"
"You should've let us know."
They were angry they wasted time waiting in line.
(Opening up)
Do you need a fork?
We need forks and knives.
This bakery's cookies are quite big.
Should I go with an elegant vibe?
He got his hopes up.
(He's serious about DCC.)
You must really like DCC.
- He was looking forward to it. - Right.
He's grabbing milk too.
(Clueless of the lie, he grabs milk too.)
You brought milk too. You know the perfect pairing.
I can't wait.
As for the plate,
- There you go. - I got us a red one.
- My gosh. - Here's your individual plate.
I'm so curious. My expectations are really high now.
Really?
But Jae Hyeon is such a nice guy.
He's not the type to be direct.
He would've said they were tasty even if they were made of poop.
- I'm curious about his reaction... - Same here.
- the moment Hyun Moo takes it out. - I'm also very curious.
I wonder how he'll react.
This place has unique packaging.
I thought, "The original ones are indeed different."
- Other places make it look pretty. - Right.
But this place... Look.
- I... - Is it just wrapped in paper?
Pretty much. Their cookies are so rustic like an old restaurant.
- Like the old-school fried chicken? - Right. The old-school chicken.
(Looking forward to it)
What kind of bakery makes rustic DCC?
He's so kind.
- Close your eyes. - Really?
- Buying them wasn't easy. - Okay.
- Don't open your eyes. - You'll put it on my hand?
I'll put it in front of you.
(Rustling)
Gosh, it sounds...
(Gosh, it even sounds different.)
What about the sound? How did it sound?
- It sounded fancy. - What are you talking about?
- It was just a plastic bag. - It was from a plastic bag.
How's that fancy?
I was already hooked.
- Gosh, it sounds... - It's different, right?
- I can hear it. - The packaging was classy.
- It sounds like paper parchment. - That's it.
- That's the authentic version. - You waited in line for this.
Can I open my eyes?
One, two, three.
(The authentic DCC is revealed!)
- That's the authentic version. - Can I open my eyes?
One, two, three.
(Gasping)
My mind went blank.
From this clip, I realized once again...
- that you're such a nice guy. - Why do you say that?
- You were ready to act impressed. - Right.
- "I should act impressed first." - I see.
He was about to frown,
but decided not to.
- Then he's trying to smile. - Right.
His facial expression in that split second is funny.
(Gasping)
(What do you think?)
(This is the authentic version of DCC?)
(Trying to hold back his laughter)
Really?
(To call it a high-end DCC, it looks quite sloppy.)
- "Really?" - "Really?"
I made it since 7am this morning.
- Wait, you made this? - Yes.
My expectations are completely ruined.
What? No.
Let me tell you something.
- You know Hue, right? - Yes.
- He asked for one more. - Really?
He said it was better than the one he had in Busan.
I'm curious about how it tastes, though.
- Let me taste it. - Okay.
(Rustling)
(Oh, my)
It sort of looks like gaetteok too.
You're lucky it's not dog poop.
You know gaetteok? The one made with mugwort.
- It's so good. - What happened to the wrapper?
Your finishing touch looks off.
- What? It looks like pursed lips. - No.
It looks like Siru's anus.
Right.
- I'll cut this in half. - Check the inside.
Check how much pistachio spread I added.
(He cuts it into bite-sized pieces.)
- Gosh. - See?
When I sliced it, I got that crunchy texture.
Of course. That's kadayif.
You know that kadayif looks like...
- thin noodles. - Right.
But my kadayif looks like this.
- They're long? - They're like kalguksu noodles.
Slicing the cookie felt like I was stepping on first snow.
- That's right. It's crunchy. - Yes.
He said it was like stepping on first snow.
How's that anything like stepping on first snow?
Gosh, he's so kind.
- The title is "First Snow." - Really?
- Oh, my. - Oh, my.
My gosh. You know you have to stretch it out like this.
Of course. That's why it's called a chewy cookie.
Gosh, this is crazy.
I'll try it.
(Putting it in his mouth without any hesitation)
His initial reaction is important.
(Crunchy)
My gosh. It sounds like he's eating a real cookie.
It sounds like you're eating radish kimchi.
Is this kadayif?
(Confused by the thick kadayif he's never had before)
(Chocking)
- The glutinous rice... Oh, my bad. - Okay.
- The marshmallows... - They got stuck in my mouth.
Right.
- I bet it got stuck on your throat. - Right.
People who had it know the difference.
- Their attitude is different. - Of course.
It's different.
Is this...
(Snorting)
(Choking)
It's stuck on your throat, right?
Yes.
Hence the name, "chewy."
It once got stuck in my throat that I couldn't talk.
(Burping)
You have indigestion, right?
(Quickly washing down the chewy cookie with milk)
It's hard to wash it down. It's so sticky.
- Do you have indigestion? - By the way...
(Crunchy)
Did that crunchy sound come from your throat?
It sounds like he's chewing on amalgam.
When I was chewing it, there was a crunchy bit.
I thought I was going to lose my tooth.
(It's not easy to chew down the kadayif.)
You know the cereal people eat in the morning?
I don't like soggy cereal.
- That's the worst. - I really like...
that crunchy texture when I take a bite of it.
And your cookie is crunchy. I'm serious.
- It's good, right? - Yes.
- It's like a scorched rice cookie. - Right.
It's not a Dubai chewy cookie. It's a Moo chewy cookie.
Even when you have it three days later,
- it will still have... - It's...
the glass-shard texture.
(Smug)
(Impressed)
Honestly, this is good.
It's just that I sound like a fool when I speak after eating it.
It messes up your pronunciation.
- Honestly, it's good. - It's good, right?
I think the glass shard cut off his tongue.
(I think the glass shard cut off his tongue.)
I'd pay money for this.
- Right? - Yes.
- Do you mean it? - I'd pay money for it.
Really? How much would you pay for this?
If you use different packaging, not this plastic bag,
- Yes. - I'd pay 11.5 dollars.
- Like a craft burger. - Then...
The packaging was pretty bad, right?
Because of the size?
He used a lot of ingredients for that.
It was good because it wasn't too sweet.
- Right. - It wasn't sweet, so it was good.
Everyone is complimenting it.
I'm curious.
Thank you for bringing the oven. Move on to your next delivery.
- He wasn't done. - You have more things to deliver?
- There's more? - That was past 9pm.
- What? - There's another one?
You didn't have to see me off.
(He didn't forget to grab the jacket from G brand.)
- I'll use it well. - Thank you for the meal.
- Bye. Thank you. - Bye.
It's 9pm now.
I'll arrive at my last stop...
at 9:30pm.
At 9:30pm?
It's like you're going around to give out wedding invitations.
You've been out all day.
(He's calling someone while driving.)
Hello.
- Sung Hwan. - Sung Hwan?
- It's Sung Hwan? - Hey.
I'll arrive at 9:24pm. Okay?
- Okay. I got it. - Okay.
What other item needs after-sales service?
It was the most important one.
(The most important after-sales service for Sung Hwan)
It's the most important one?
It has something to do with you too.
Me?
This is the place. I've arrived.
(Finally,)
(he arrives at Sung Hwan's house for the most important job.)
You're good at parking.
- He's so good at parking. - Yes.
He's a great driver.
My gosh, I'm full.
I was so full that day.
Wait, did you eat again at his house?
- I'm going to Sung Hwan's house. - Right.
My gosh. It's...
night now.
When you have a long day, you can think,
"I'll sleep like a baby tonight."
That lifts your spirit a bit.
I always sleep like a baby.
- I pass out every day. - Really?
(I can sleep like a baby after this.)
Gosh, there's no elevator.
No elevator for me.
(Walking up)
Gosh, this is...
(Sniffing)
It must be the unit with the delicious smell, right?
You could smell delicious food?
All the units from the second floor and up smelled so good.
I guess he prepared a lot of food.
(Pushing up)
(Beeping)
Come here.
No.
- He's wearing an apron. - No.
Who is it?
Open up.
He just got here.
I thought your passcode was 1818.
(Joking)
Kkotbun.
- Hyun Moo. - Kkotbun.
- Gosh, she's excited. - Your shoes...
Kkotbun.
- Kkotbun. - You've never met Kkotbun, right?
- Kkotbun. She likes me. - What's all that?
- Gosh. - I'll show them to you later.
- Hyun Moo. - Yes.
Take a look.
It's...
- Okay. Play with Kkotbun first. - Kkotbun.
(Moomoo, the dog expert, meets Kkotbun in person.)
Kkotbun.
- You... - Sung Hwan looks different today.
He looks like a well-built housewife, right?
(A well-built housewife)
- Hyun Moo. - Yes.
These are my favorite art pieces.
As you can see in my house, I actually like art.
- That's your taste in art. - Santorini.
- Santorini. - Oh, this is Santorini.
- It says, "taco," not Santorini. - Listen.
He thinks it's Santorini if it's not Korea.
Oh, this is Santorini. And...
I have your painting, one of my favorites...
along with my other favorite pieces.
But I placed yours all the way in the front before everything.
- Before everything. I like art. - You like art.
The last stop of Moomoo's After-Sales Service is...
the man who will get the Grand Award Air.
It's Sung Hwan's house.
(Moosquiat's new painting, "Moomoo Market")
(I like the painting.)
(He purchased it for 500 dollars.)
(And Sung Hwan had his eyes on this item.)
(The Grand Award Air when he won the award)
(I'll pay 600 dollars for both.)
(He donated a total of 1,000 dollars for everything.)
At the bazaar, CODE KUNST brought the bottle.
I'm delivering it on his behalf.
Since he's the first client to buy my art,
I'll tell him where to place it. I'm like a curator.
- Come here, Hyun Moo. - Give me a tour of your house.
Yes. But it got cold. I didn't want to waste time for you.
So I already prepared it.
- What? - My gosh. What's that?
- Gnocchi? - Gnocchi.
(Have some gnocchi.)
- So I already prepared it. - He wanted to feed me too.
(I already had three meals.)
Everyone gave you food when you visited them.
I hadn't felt this loved in a while.
I saw it coming.
I could smell food the moment I started to walk up the stairs.
I knew it. "He's cooking."
But I was so full already.
(Feeling bloated)
- You'll be surprised by the taste. - Okay.
(Chuckling)
It's very tasty. Now comes something we like.
- That's right. - It's really tasty.
Do another round of pepper.
I thought you wouldn't like it. I prefer it that way too.
"I thought you wouldn't like it."
(Full of pepper)
- Are you serious? - Of course.
It isn't much when you mix it in.
(I love pepper.)
Why are you guys having a match of pride?
I like it much more.
- Hyun Moo, please sit there. - Okay.
Kkotbun.
Hyun Moo, it's only a small amount.
(Feeling bloated)
I had four meals.
(I had four meals.)
- Stop giving me food. - Do you know what it is?
- Olive oil. - Gosh!
- Truffle. - Truffle oil?
- It's expensive. - You need to add truffle oil.
You need to add an excessive amount.
- Do you smell it? - I smell it.
- It looks so tasty. - Gnocchi.
- It looks tasty. - Right?
Yes.
Even if you're full, try a bite...
- because I'll eat the rest. - I'll try it.
- Try it. - You made it with effort.
(I'll try it. You made it with effort.)
It's tasty.
Thank you for the food.
Be honest.
Honestly, how does it taste? How is this amateur's cooking skill?
- It's good, right? - Listen.
Did you add Cheongyang chili for spiciness?
I added peperoncino.
- It's so tasty. - It's so tasty, right?
It isn't even about the truffle oil. The sauce is so tasty.
- It's so tasty, right? - Yes.
The sauce was tasty.
- Seriously. - It's tasty.
(He takes another big bite.)
It looks tasty.
- You want to add more pasta, right? - Yes.
- It's tasty. - You have my approval.
- Yes. - You know,
I like the spicy aftertaste.
You like that, right?
- Yes. - A place in Jongno makes this.
It's really nice.
When someone visits your place,
you give a beverage or fruits,
not a meal.
But all four of them gave me a meal.
One of them could've given me fruits or a beverage.
I wouldn't have complained.
I felt the Korean way of showing love.
They have a lot of love. They're warmhearted.
(Dazed)
I'm practically in a trance.
(Meanwhile, Sung Hwan...)
My stomach hurts. I ate so much.
Jae Hyeon gave me curry.
My stomach...
(He inhales gnocchi without a break.)
He ate more than me.
(Laughing)
After Sung Hwan scoops up food,
he slows down before putting it in his mouth.
- Really? - He wants to eat with precision.
- Does he smell the food first? - Yes.
I think he does that.
Look. He slows down.
You're right.
- He slows down. - Yes.
I think it's a fatty's trait.
You're calling him a fatty outright.
(Sorry)
(Eating)
- Stay here for a second. - Okay.
- You're going to eat more, right? - No.
- No. - Kkotbun.
Kkotbun, come here. It's okay.
Is that so? It's okay.
- Come here. - He's a dog expert.
You punk.
She's so nice.
As for this one,
I've always wanted to make you try it.
- What? He said it wasn't food. - What?
- Try what? - It's something simple.
I'm serious. Just have a taste.
It's a simple dessert.
- We had pasta just now, right? - Yes.
- So a dessert is a must. - Yes.
It's very simple.
Right. Sung Hwan must have a dessert after a meal.
It's a must.
I also have something I want you to try.
I'm serious. Just have a taste.
You look so pretty...
unlike your owner.
You look so pretty.
- How cute. - She's so cute.
There you go.
Seriously, I can't believe you'll finally try it.
- What is it? - Is it ice cream?
- Stop feeding me. - Hyun Moo, you must try it.
My goodness.
(Feeling excited to feed Hyun Moo, he prepares the dessert.)
- What is it? I'm curious. - Right.
You're so pretty.
What's that?
(He tops it with soaked bread.)
(Then he covers it with white sauce.)
All done.
(He wraps up by sprinkling powder on the top.)
Is it cinnamon?
It's tiramisu. Am I right?
- Tiramisu? - That's right.
- Is it tiramisu? - You figured it out right away.
Decorations are important.
- Coffee-flavored jelly? - Jelly.
Jelly?
- Don't say anything. - Okay.
- Let me just feel it. - Okay.
There you go. Eat it with the bread.
- Is this good? - That's good.
(A harmonious spoonful with the coffee, cream, and bread)
It's bound to be tasty.
(Sniffing)
It's nice, right?
Savor the cream.
(He puts it in his mouth...)
(and savors the taste.)
It's really tasty, right?
Do you see why I added the jelly?
It's tasty.
- It tastes like tiramisu. - It does, right?
There are two types of tiramisu.
- The thick one and... - He brings it over to him.
He isn't listening.
the watery one.
(He scoops some out naturally and puts it in his mouth.)
He was building up to eat it himself.
So you'll eat the entire thing after I get a taste.
It's really tasty, right?
Gosh, I'm exhausted. Gosh.
(Feeling stuffed, Moomoo leans into the sofa.)
It's really tasty.
Had it been my first house,
I would've gotten two refills.
He takes big bites.
It must be tasty.
(The owner of the house inhales it instead of the full guest.)
(He empties the container.)
Sung Hwan is eating everything with the guest sitting next to him.
- You aren't full yet, right? - Of course not.
How long did it take to make it?
It took me a day since I had to rest it.
Exclude the resting time. For how long did you work on it?
Not long.
How many minutes? About 30 minutes?
About ten minutes.
As for me,
I spent four hours.
(As for me, I spent over four hours.)
- I made something. - Wait, what did you make?
I...
How should I explain it?
Firstly,
I made it because it was popular.
Two people tasted it and gave me rave reviews.
One person had it at a famous place in Busan,
but my version was tastier.
(He had it in Busan, but Hyun Moo's version was tastier.)
(I see.)
- I have a hunch. - What's your guess?
- The legendary cookie? - What's your guess?
- Don. - Don?
- Don. - What?
- What's that? - Don chewy cookie.
- Don chewy cookie? - Yes.
Is it made of pork?
Isn't it called don chewy cookie?
I guess he's craving pork belly.
Sung Hwan is bad with names.
I really don't know the answer.
(He doesn't know the name of the legendary cookie.)
Isn't it called don chewy cookie?
Du.
(Du?)
- Dubai! - Dubai.
What's the rest? Dubai...
Chewy cookie.
- Correct. - Really?
This is what it looks like.
You have so much self-love. You named it Moo chewy cookie.
Since I've had it, I'll compare it to what you've made.
Sung Hwan is serious about desserts.
Among the four people I've met today,
he's the most sensitive about desserts.
He's serious about them.
- He's delicate. - Yes.
(A dessert is a must after a meal.)
(My goodness)
(He calls himself a dessert lover.)
He has eaten a lot of desserts,
so he can't help but be sensitive.
(Sung Hwan can't help but have sensitive tastes.)
You must be nervous.
It's like getting judged on "Culinary Class Wars."
I'll try it, Hyun Moo.
Sung Hwan will make a straightforward assessment.
- That's right. - He'll be coolheaded about it.
How big was the Dubai chewy cookie you had?
It was this big.
- It was that big, right? - It was this big.
(Taking out)
(Oh, my!)
- This is... - Try it.
Can I open it and eat it?
- Hold on. - Cut it.
Dubai chewy cookie isn't so...
You're the first one...
who doesn't mind the plastic bag.
What do you mean?
Hue said that it looked like a poop bag.
I mean...
(Dropping)
- He has a weak stomach. - He has a weak stomach.
- I mean... - The color is similar too.
- I'll do it. - Hurry up.
It's okay.
- He's coughing. - He won't be able to eat it.
Hold on. It looks like...
This is...
(An unfortunate appearance)
Poop chewy cookie.
(Laughing)
It's the elephant chewy cookie.
- Gosh. - The elephant chewy cookie.
Hyun Moo, do you know that I have a weak stomach?
Listen.
While it looks unappetizing...
I mean, why does it look wet?
- Does it look wet? - It's...
It keeps getting on his nerve.
I hate that it's wet.
It contains so many good ingredients.
(Hold on. There's one more.)
(He rolls out one more.)
Did you wrap it up?
Gosh, what's that?
It was a bit...
What's that?
I think Kkotbun pooped from the above.
(The unfortunate appearance makes them feel dizzy.)
(I don't want to look at it.)
There's no smell,
but I feel like I can smell it.
Did you wrap it up?
(Poop chewy cookie rolls over without a warning.)
All right.
(My goodness)
I mean...
Seriously, that's...
Hyun Moo, I'm not joking.
Hyun Moo, ask Ju Seung.
If I see something like this during a trip,
I hate it so much.
Do you know how many times I shower in a day?
Sung Hwan,
- try it. - I mean...
(The appearance moves him already.)
- He's crying. - I blended the pistachio.
- This is canola oil. - Okay, I'll try it.
- This one... - Okay.
It looks wet because of canola oil.
- I see. Oil. - Yes.
I'll be completely honest.
Of course, it's tasty.
(He cautiously takes a bite of the matcha MCC.)
(Crunchy)
Gosh, Hyun Moo.
- It's fricking good, right? - It must be tasty.
- You approve, right? - I approve.
- You approve, right? - Yes.
Of course. He's serious about desserts.
It just looks unappetizing.
In a sense, the ingredient is better.
I'm so curious.
I want to get Bum June's approval.
It's sticky, right?
It should be called DSC.
Dubai sticky cookie.
It's tasty.
It's stickier since it contains more marshmallow.
- You're right. - Yes.
It's much better than what I had in Gangnam.
- Is that so? - Really?
I'm serious. I loved how satisfying the texture was.
- Better than the Gangnam version? - Much better.
I did it.
It's good.
Jae Hyeon couldn't speak after eating one earlier.
(Everyone approves of the taste.)
There's a reason why I'm here.
Are we going somewhere?
No, there's a reason why I'm here.
Moomoo's After-Sales Service.
Yes.
What you wanted the most...
was...
this one.
Finally.
(Reverent)
Seriously.
I can't believe it makes him reverent.
It even went into...
the recycling bin at my place two times.
It didn't get recycled.
I took it out in the end, thinking,
- "It was Hyun Moo's gift." - That's disgusting.
- This one... - After I won the Grand Prize...
Jun Hyun Moo.
(The touching moment of receiving the Grand Prize)
I scooped up the air of the place.
- You didn't open it once, right? - No, I didn't.
It's the exact same air.
It hasn't been opened once.
- Really? - Of course.
(Air of the 2022 Grand Prize)
How much did I pay for this?
(I'll pay 600 dollars!)
He wasted money.
When you have something like that...
It gives off energy.
Even if it doesn't actually give off energy,
- it affects your mindset. - Exactly.
- That's right. - It's the placebo effect.
If something good happens,
- you go, "Is it because of that?" - That's right.
- It's a nice cycle. - That's right.
If Sung Hwan becomes more successful afterward,
- It'll be incredible. - it'll be incredible.
- That's right. - I'm curious about his future.
It'll be thanks to his hard work, but...
- Hundred percent. - Still...
- Still... - Such items make you determined.
- That's right. - That's right.
It was a tiring day,
but I'm in a good mood.
In any case, the items found new homes.
I saw how well the items were doing with the new owners.
And whether or not I messed it up,
I made something by working hard for 4 to 5 hours...
and people enjoyed it.
I was happy to give it as a gift.
Although my body was exhausted, my mind wasn't.
I applaud Moomoo...
for doing a good job despite some disappointment.
(Clapping)
(Moomoo, well done.)
Hyun Moo, do you want to see...
- my favorite place? - Show me.
(The Repair Work of the Mind Is Complete.)
Kkotbun, do you like it?
Kkotbun, we're nearly there.
(Seoul Station)
(Looking for the Square Excitement)
- Square? - Square?
(4:50am, Seoul Station)
- It's too early in the morning. - It's dawn.
Did it rain?
(CODE KUNST waits for someone early in the morning.)
It was my first time leaving the house so early.
There he is.
(Someone walks over from afar.)
What? It's Lee Dong Hwi.
Dong Hwi.
Gosh, Sung Woo.
(In dramas such as "Reply 1988" and "Big Bet,")
(he gave a good performance as a scene stealer.)
("The Roundup: Punishment," "Veteran," "Extreme Job")
(The irreplaceable actor swept movies that got ten million views.)
(During the Seorae Outlet)
(You got very distorted.)
(How could you tell someone that he got distorted?)
(With Hyun Moo, he showed off the distorted chemistry.)
(His chemistry with CODE KUNST was like the married fashionistas.)
They have the same vibes.
Gosh, Sung Woo.
When did we become close?
It has been a while.
About seven years ago, he told me that he loved my music.
Since I loved his work as well,
we became close.
The two of them are like soulmates.
- Dong Hwi. - What?
(He sticks in his hand.)
This area is particularly cold.
The shoulder area is particularly cold.
Maybe he fell down on his way.
Maybe he came across a wild boar.
I get that Dong Hwi is fashionable.
Despite that,
- he looks like a beggar. - On purpose...
He looks like he feeds pigeons.
(He looks like a pigeon man.)
Did you choose an outfit for the Seoul Station?
(An outfit for the time, place, and occasion)
No.
I didn't do that.
- It's my favorite coat. - It looks ridiculous.
I threw on my usual items...
so that I wouldn't be late.
Stick in your hand if you're cold.
It's my favorite brand.
The designer will be upset.
But people might misunderstand.
I never expected Dong Hwi to get humiliated for his outfit.
You look very different without the coat.
Of course.
He looks much better.
The KTX train is more spacious than I expected.
(Looking around)
Isn't this the fastest way to go to Busan?
- Of course. - Right?
- Busan. - KTX.
We love block toys.
We heard about a unique treasure house...
- in Busan, - Really?
so we decided to visit.
I usually go to bed around 3am.
Unlike me,
Dong Hwi is a total morning person.
I had to adjust to his schedule if I wanted to travel with him,
so I did that.
It's best to travel with someone you get along with.
(Thus, CODE KUNST and Dong Hwi set out to find the block toys.)
- Do both of you like block toys? - Yes.
It's fascinating that you're going to Busan for them.
There could be...
- unique vintage items. - That's right.
(Staring)
It feels nice for some reason.
I haven't taken KTX in a long while.
- I take it often. - It has been 3 or 4 years.
- If I'm filming in the countryside, - Okay.
I part with my manager at the Seoul Station.
- Why? - I live nearby.
I live near the Seoul Station.
(Does he live near the Seoul Station?)
Is the Seoul Station really your house?
(It's no wonder his outfit had the homeless vibe.)
The Seoul Station isn't my house.
- Then these trains are your cars. - No.
When you think about it,
trains feel safe.
I love taking trains.
Why do you love trains so much?
I'm a fan.
I'm a fan of KTX.
He bought a ticket, right?
People might misunderstand.
(The train stops for a second.)
So...
The European group hasn't been decided.
- Mexico is the hosting country. - Yes.
So the list of matches is nice.
You suit Mexico for some reason.
- I know what you mean. - Right?
- I see it. - I think it's because of...
"Big Bet."
- The dark figures? - Yes.
- The dark figures. - Yes.
- It's a men's drama. - "Big Bet" is a masterpiece.
I'm saying this after the popularity died down.
Why did you do that to Moo Sik?
(Choi Min Sik's character)
Seriously, so many people scold me for it.
I want to see him. I want to see him one day.
Anytime. Min Sik likes you a lot.
- Really? - He likes you a lot. Yes.
When I ask him whether he knows who CODE KUNST is,
he goes, "Of course. That big-eared guy?"
Seriously. He comes up...
He comes up with a nickname for everyone. He knows everyone.
He knows everyone.
I'll entertain him if I meet him.
I'll do something.
(The big-eared guy is determined.)
(It's still dark outside.)
- What time is it? - Dear passengers,
- It's only 7:30am. - for your pleasant trip...
(Yawning)
He must be tired.
How many hours of sleep did you get?
- Two hours. - My goodness.
How long has it been since you went to Jeju Island?
- I visit Jeju Island often. - Really?
I went to Jeju Island recently for the 1st time in 10 years.
Everything seemed unfamiliar.
How old are you now?
I filmed Byung Jae's contents yesterday, so...
He isn't letting CODE KUNST sleep.
He's keeping CODE KUNST awake.
(The night owl becomes more worn out.)
CODE KUNST can't sleep even though he wants to.
(Energetic)
Did he get 20 hours of sleep the night before?
He hadn't come outside in a while.
So he was excited.
(His mouth moves without a break.)
Dong Hwi is just like his character in "Reply 1988."
- Should we sleep for a while now? - He mustered up his courage.
(I'm sorry. This is it for me.)
(Slightly disappointed)
(CODE KUNST falls asleep just like that.)
He looks so young.
- Is he talking to himself? - He's talking to himself?
I had fun back then.
So he kept talking to himself like that.
(While CODE KUNST was sleeping,)
(he kept going through his phone.)
He's amazing.
(He fiddled around for a while after that.)
Gosh, the weather is great.
(Dong Hwi is still wide awake.)
He must've been really excited.
(Heart beating)
(Peeking)
"Hurry up and get up, so you can talk to me."
Soon, we will arrive at the last station, Busan Station.
(Soon, we will arrive at the last station, Busan Station.)
(Tapping)
This is Busan.
As if it's some kind of confession.
- Right? - Yes.
- Sung Woo. - Yes?
Let's talk a lot today.
(Let's talk a lot today.)
Oh, my gosh!
Let's get off now.
- That gave me the goosebumps. - Gosh.
Gosh, Busan Station has become a lot better.
Right.
Gosh.
Isn't this Busan?
It suits Busan Station as well.
It suits the stations well.
Stations abroad can work as well.
Right.
Gosh, isn't this Busan?
Isn't this Busan?
This is Busan, isn't it?
- Isn't the milmyeon here great? - Gosh.
Seriously. Busan is good.
Busan is good.
Busan is good, isn't it?
You know that Busan people hate people talking like that, don't you?
- Right. - With the sloppy accent.
You want to speak in their accent for some reason.
- Right. - "Are you here?"
It's a sign of being...
- happy to be in Busan. - Right.
Check that out.
There's Industrial Bank of Korea.
"Industrial Bank of Korea."
(Speaking in weird accent)
- "Industrial Bank of Korea." - Is that even right?
He's into it.
Dong Hwi! You know that, don't you?
You watched the movie, "Ode to My Father," right?
Of course, I did.
There was a place I planned for us to visit today,
but it opens at 2pm.
I want to go to Gukje Market.
If it opens at 2pm, something is incredibly off.
- But... - "Something is incredibly off."
But it's just a waste to go to Busan...
- just for that one thing. - There are so many things to eat.
There are many places to visit.
But the train tickets for the later times were all sold out.
- Really? - I had to be quick.
- Oh, right. - After you.
- It's a chance to look around. - Hello.
- Gukje Market Intersection, please. - Gukje Market.
It's my first time visiting Gukje Market.
- Really? - Yes.
It's a famous market.
- Of course. - I've never been there as well.
- There are so many things to see. - I've just heard of its name a lot.
- Right. - Right.
- I've never been there as well. - Really?
The driver might not have let Dong Hwi in on his own...
thinking he'd have no money.
(He's moving around comfortably thanks to CODE KUNST.)
- This is it. - Gosh!
- Goodbye. - Thank you. Stay healthy, sir.
Thank you.
Shall we get going then?
Okay.
It feels great to be at a place like this after a while.
- Right. - Yes.
This is the main street.
(In front of Gukje Market,)
Is this Busan?
(BIFF Square unfolds.)
It's a place of my memories.
I always went there after the film festival.
Really?
(Thinking about those times)
(When you walk straight down,)
(Gwangbok-ro Fashion Street)
(Busan's main fashion street appears.)
There aren't many people as it's the morning.
Right now...
There aren't many young people at this time.
It's an escape room!
(They move slowly while looking around.)
It's a gacha shop.
"Busan Champ Boxing."
You know the way, right?
I guess it will soon appear.
(I don't know the way.)
You like roaming around as well, don't you?
- I enjoy doing that a lot. - Right?
Even when I have a shoot,
I keep roaming around.
- That's the best part. - You do that?
That's the best part.
That's the best part. Roaming around with no destination.
What?
(He spots something.)
- Dong Hwi. - Yes?
Your outfit suits this place perfectly.
(Mr. Lee with a poor outfit)
(Is he about to get arrested?)
What?
(He spots something.)
- Dong Hwi. - Yes?
Your outfit suits this place perfectly.
Go inside and say hello.
(He drags him away quickly in case he gets arrested.)
I made a big mistake.
I'm suffering so much after deciding to wear this.
He looks like the Street King.
Gosh.
- It looks great. - What is this place?
- Art Cinema? - The Art Cinema...
- plays independent films. - I see.
It's continually being supported by Busan.
- I'm serious about this. - Right.
You suit the movie posters really well.
- Do you think so? - Yes.
I suit that movie perfectly right now.
"Two Seasons, Two Strangers."
I look just like a traveler.
("Two Seasons, Two Strangers")
It looks like you're part of the poster!
- Right. - Your outfit is insane!
- It's an amazing outfit. - It can do so many things!
- The designer is amazing. - I'm jealous.
- It strangely suits anything. - It's so versatile.
That suits a war movie as well.
- Right. - Right.
- Aren't I right? - It suits anything.
- "71: Into the Fire." - "North Korea's Southern Army."
- Right. - "North Korea's Southern Army."
You can do anything in that outfit.
I started feeling jealous starting from that moment.
It looks like you're part of the poster!
I must be escaping right now.
I'm not someone who suits movie posters.
CODE KUNST's fashion looks rather normal.
You look like someone who isn't interested in fashion.
It's hard to pull off that yellow padded jacket.
- Right. - Right.
- You look too normal. - Right.
(His opponent was way too strong.)
Right. This is Jungang Cathedral. I remember this place now.
There are many clothing stores on both sides.
- So this is it. - Right.
This place is known as the Vintage Street.
Vintage Street.
(Walking up)
(Stopping)
(Pointing)
I want to go there.
The vintage store looks really nice.
Right. It caught my attention.
- Gosh. - It looks like a pork cutlet place.
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
Gosh, there are so many cute outfits.
(It's full of stylish vintage outfits.)
As I've been gaining more experience...
based on the vintage market,
I'm quite confident now.
When I visit a vintage store,
I know what I must buy and what I must not buy.
Dong Hwi also has a lot of experience.
We went in as if we were going in for a cup of coffee.
You have to choose wisely when it comes to vintage clothing.
- But they're both fashion people. - Right.
You shouldn't have the heart of wanting to buy something.
You go in with the heart of not wanting to buy anything.
Why is that? Is it because...
When you go in with the heart of wanting to buy something,
you buy something that isn't needed.
- Right. - But it's the real deal...
if you still find something you really want.
- Something you really need. - It will be a gem.
It will be something you really need.
This one looks nice.
(The CODE DONG Brothers start their search.)
- There are a lot of nice ones. - Right.
It has to feel like you found a gem at a place like this.
- A gem? - Right.
It has to feel like, "I bought this in Busan."
- Right. - Right.
- "Oh, right." - "Where did I buy this?"
- It can't be like that. - Right.
"I bought this in Busan."
This is the conversation of the experts.
When you go to a place like that...
and buy something without any gain or benefit,
it will be meaningless.
It would be better to just get a brand new outfit.
- Right. - Right.
-Right. - There should be a price benefit...
or it should be a rare item.
There should be at least one kind of benefit.
But it's hard for us to know if it's a rare item.
We don't know how to distinguish them.
It shouldn't be based on brands.
There are items that are hard to find after a trend is over.
Certain designs were a trend in certain periods.
- We aren't aware of that. - We aren't aware of that.
How are we supposed to know that?
- We aren't aware of that. - Right.
That is why we only focus on the brands.
(Searching thoroughly)
They're searching really thoroughly.
It's because they know what they're looking through.
- They look great. - That must be exciting.
Dong Hwi checks the details a lot more than I do.
- He looks different. - Gosh.
(During the outlet that CODE KUNST opened the other time,)
(he pulled off any outfit.)
The pants are a bit too big.
(He finds something extraordinary again.)
Did he lose his style as well?
(Laughing)
What do you think?
(How do I look?)
But it looks nice.
It looks different with Dong Hwi wearing it.
It looks better than his look on the left.
(He dressed himself with a fancy tone of red.)
It looks off because of the color of his undershirt.
- If it isn't that color... - It would look much better.
Check out the color of his pants.
(He pulls off the intense color combination.)
I'll go and get changed.
(Shall I try out an outfit as well?)
I'm curious about how he'll look.
(The front-runner of trendy styling)
- You look amazing. - He looks different.
- This looks cute. - Will you try it on?
(A leather jacket catches his attention.)
(Throwing on)
(Impressed)
- Gosh, this looks cute. - It's your jacket.
- It suits you. - Right.
- It's a good type of leather... - Right.
- that feels very soft. - Gosh, he looks amazing.
(I look even better when I slick back my hair.)
- Gosh, this one looks nice. - Gosh.
(I like this one.)
When it comes to leather or knitwear,
new products are too expensive.
The price goes up by 5 to 6 times for new products.
As for T-shirts or dress shirts, the price of new products...
aren't that different from vintage stores.
That is why I tend to focus...
on leather or knitwear in vintage stores.
When you buy a new leather product,
- you have to break into it. - It will feel stiff.
But the ones in vintage stores are already broken into.
- It will fit a lot more naturally. - Right.
I told my stylist...
that I wanted to dress like you.
Let's go shopping together.
- Really? I would love to do that. - It won't suit you.
- You should go with me. Why him? - Just set a price.
Ji Hyeon...
is at an easy level. Anything can be thrown over him.
What about me?
You should give up on fashion now.
Why? I just got started!
(In the bloody fashion battle,)
(Hyun Moo got humiliated after losing to Kian84.)
Why cling to something that has no meaning?
Why do you keep saying that?
You know this, don't you?
The ones that are hung up on their own...
- Right. - are special.
represent the pride of the owners.
- They're special ones. - Those ones must be expensive.
Right.
What? Where did this come from?
(I think I found another special one.)
(By the fishy)
(He automatically sings the background song...)
(while trying on the leather jacket.)
You look different now.
It's a bit small.
He looks like a detective from the past.
This is fascinating.
Clothes are this important.
(By the fishy)
He keeps turning into a new character.
He's a true actor.
- A man with a thousand faces. - This is nice.
There's a Burberry coat.
This one suits him as well.
This one feels like his character in "Big Bet."
(A white jacket that can express one's wealth)
I mentioned this before.
When people dress up strangely...
(When people dress up strangely...)
When people dress up strangely, they are called stylish.
You've set your standards now.
They weren't chosen to be bought.
- He's just trying them on. - He's just trying them on.
Right.
"This won't suit me."
- You should try it on. - Then, you should try it on.
- That way, you can really tell. - You might find something...
out of the blue.
What is fashion?
(Fashion is too hard for me.)
But for me,
my outfit looks the most vintage and appealing to me.
I'm serious.
Check this out.
I'm sorry, sir.
Would you like to take a look?
(Ta-da)
- Look. - I would get that.
(A fantastic vintage look)
(I would get that too.)
I will get this one.
(Joking)
It looks like an artwork.
This one caught my eye, though.
Everything here looks good on you.
It isn't that easy to find a red like this.
The mood suits you perfectly.
Isn't it the same red?
(Is there a difference?)
They all look different even with the same red.
There's no thing as the same red.
What a line.
The red seen there is different from this red.
It's not like I'm colorblind.
You're looking down on him so much.
Do you think I'm blind or what?
That's not it. My eyes are perfectly fine.
Right.
This is what I mean.
It's hard to find the right red...
- that suits my preferred style. - Right.
So those things can be seen.
It's perfect for you.
It's 58 dollars.
- That's a great price. - He should get it right away.
I should tuck it in.
- That one looks nice. - Right.
I would get that if I were you.
- Really? - Yes.
It's hard to find this kind of pattern.
- This one is hard to find. - Right.
This is unique on its own.
So it isn't that expensive.
Gosh, the women's clothes are insane.
I would get this right away if I were a woman.
- It looks nice. - Should I get it for my mom?
It looks nice.
(He shops for his mother's clothes as well.)
I should get these for my mom.
- Yes, my son? - Mom!
- Yes? - Actually...
Oh, right. Say hi.
- Hello, ma'am! - Hello!
- It's a pleasure to meet you. - It's Dong Hwi.
Gosh!
It's a celebrity!
(Gosh! It's a celebrity.)
Mom.
I'm in a vintage store in Busan.
- Right. - I chose these for you...
because they looked so nice.
- Take a look at them. - Right.
- I think they will fit you. - Gosh, what a sweet son.
He's so sweet.
- I'm jealous. - What a great son.
We're like best buddies together.
It has to be long.
- It's really long. - Right.
- It's long. - Right.
- Also, - Right.
- this one looks really nice. - I think it will suit her well.
It's a short-sleeved turtleneck sweater.
I don't like ones that have a pattern.
Is that so?
- I like things with single colors. - This is just one color.
Okay then.
Okay.
- Thank you! - Okay. Bye.
Bye.
Moms say they don't like everything.
But they wear it when given to them.
They would feel happy about it.
- Moms are like that. - Moms are like that.
But that's the only thing she wears these days.
- I see. - Really?
After putting on,
she kept asking me to take a picture.
(She must really like it.)
(Perfectly styled for his mother)
(Feeling proud)
It would be great if you could wrap these up, sir.
You did well to buy them.
- Thank you. - This bag is cute as well.
- Gosh, thank you. - Thank you.
- Stay healthy. - I will wear them nicely.
Let's go!
(They get done with clothes shopping before going to the toy store.)
(Shall we start walking again?)
That jacket seems to get shabbier by the minute.
- The holes get bigger. - That's the charm of it.
The holes look bigger than they were in the morning.
(He walks around with the bigger holes.)
I smell pizza.
- Where? - That's the head store...
- of L Pizza. - There's another one!
Since 1992.
I heard that place was really famous these days.
You have to try that place. The pizza is amazing.
I really want to try some.
We should get some pizza then.
Right. We should break the stereotype...
- Having gukbap in Busan. - of having gukbap in Busan.
But it looks like he should get some right now.
(With his outfit)
Pizza or gukbap? He should just get something to eat.
(Is his stomach growling?)
That's the head store.
- Let's go there! - Right.
There's a line.
There are 15 groups waiting.
- There are 15 groups waiting. - Gosh!
There are 15 groups waiting?
It was still the morning.
Then let's go there.
There's another one over there.
Let's go.
But what was fascinating...
was that it was a ten-second walk between the two head stores.
It must be the same there.
The customers would've thought of the same thing.
Doesn't this make you want to have it even more?
(Thinking positively)
Gukbap is completely out of my interest.
- But this place... - There's no line!
- has no line. - Let's go.
Let's go.
- Why is that? - Why is that?
Why does this place have no line?
- Welcome. - Hello.
But right after we went in,
a line was formed.
Right.
- It was the same here? - Right.
I think it's my first time having pizza in Busan.
- There are so many of them. - This is the best one.
- We should get the best one. - Right.
We should get the best one.
- We should get a large one. - Right.
- I'm starving right now. - I could tell.
What about this? The crust.
(The CODE DONG Brothers place their order swiftly.)
I'll pay for it.
- Gosh, this is embarrassing. - It was my idea to come here.
This is embarrassing.
I shouldn't be letting the younger one pay.
- Right. - I really want to try it.
I wonder how good the pizza here is.
Exactly.
It's a representative place in Busan.
It must be like Daejeon's S bakery.
- Right. - Right.
(The CODE DONG Brothers look around the restaurant.)
I've never seen a pizza place this crowded like that.
- It's still the morning as well. - Right.
- Your pizza is here. - Right.
Enjoy your meal.
Thank you.
It looks delicious.
It looks very familiar.
Right. It looks like a regular pizza.
It was insane.
- Here. - You should eat first.
You go first. Give me your plate.
It's a standard pizza.
There's so much cheese.
(Satisfied)
It's so good.
The cheese looks great.
- It looks good. - It looks good. I'm hungry.
It sounds like you're eating noodles.
- It's really good. - It's good.
Shall I call it the luck...
of the ones with no plan?
For example,
if we came with a plan to have pork gukbap,
we would've had to have pork gukbap no matter what.
We were able to go with the flow without coming with a plan.
(They had luck to have the pizza as they didn't have a plan.)
(He's already on his second slice.)
Burgers are the best.
(He even gets done with his third slice.)
If you ate three slices, that's really a lot.
But it was really good.
(Taking a big bite)
He used to have only one piece a day.
(Bursting with the taste of spontaneity)
(Groaning)
That was a good meal.
It makes my blood sugar spike.
- I think we should walk. - Right. Let's walk.
- I'm full. - I'm so full.
(They finish their meal before going to the block cafe.)
- It's the same. - When they ask...
if their cat is cute,
I'd go, "Not as cute as Siru."
My cats, Saebyeok and Mora, are much cuter.
It's always your cat that's the cutest.
That's how it is.
There are more people now.
- Hello. - Hi.
- Dong Hwi, until our destination... - Yes.
We have two more hours.
So...
- A schedule that's gone wrong. - It's unplanned, indeed.
Since we have two hours...
- What? - A cat cafe?
(Throwing a cat punch)
(CODE Dong Brothers were heading to the Gukje Market.)
The cafe we are supposed to go to is right here.
I've never been to a cat cafe.
"A kind-hearted cafe for stray cats..."
"where your visit becomes a donation."
We went to the cafe because stray cats stay there.
It's a cafe where stray cats...
can stay as a shelter.
Siru was in a situation where the owner couldn't keep it anymore.
I adopted it from a free adoption site...
when it was ten months old.
Dong Hwi also adopted cats...
that had nowhere else to go.
(He adopted stray cats and is raising them.)
Dong Hwi and I share that common ground.
Guys.
Guys. Come here.
There are many people like him in front of Seoul Station.
It still feels like they're in Seoul.
Nemo.
- Nemo. - Come here.
Wait.
(Crowded)
They only go to you.
Rio.
Guys, I have one too.
I have one too.
(Laughing)
I have one here too.
Nemo.
- It's so cute. - It's so cute, right?
- It's like Garfield. - It's a chubby cat.
Are there cats under here too?
- Gosh, what? - What is it?
There's a bunch underneath.
What?
- There are so many under here. - They're hiding.
Why are cats so cute?
- Gosh. You're so cute. - Oh, it's that one.
Goodness. Heedong? Its name is Heedong.
Heedong.
Momo?
- Ray. - That one must be blind.
- Which one? - This one.
(A cat with limited eyesight, Moa)
It can't see? Oh, no.
- Its legs look a bit... - Right.
It's okay.
(Approaching)
CODE KUNST must smell good to the cats.
It's the pizza.
(The smell of pizza)
You spoiled the touching moment.
Moa.
- Gosh. It must hurt. - It's okay.
- Still... - It's really timid.
And it can't see, so it doesn't like anyone touching it.
- Goodness. - Come here.
- It's okay. - It's staying still.
He handles cats well.
I've been a cat owner for over ten years.
Right. It must know.
(Stretching its legs)
- It must like it. - What?
That cat weighed on my mind.
It looked like it was opening up to me.
I found that sentiment really lovely.
That's the most memorable for me.
(Approaching)
Do you like cats?
(Nodding)
Would you be able to say which cat is cuter...
if we show you the photos of our cats?
- Come on, Dong Hwi. - Our cats' photos.
On the count of three...
Choose which cat is cuter.
Choose the cat you find cute.
(The pride of the cat owners is at stake.)
- In 1, 2, 3. - In 1, 2, 3.
- Both are cute. - That's too bad.
They're both really pretty.
(Which one will the kid choose?)
- In 1, 2, 3. - In 1, 2, 3.
(CODE Dong Brothers' cats, which one is the cutest?)
- Both are cute. - That's too bad.
They're both really pretty.
Three.
(Picking one without contemplating)
Dong Hwi.
- Look closely again. - It's cute, right?
- It's the apple that's cute. - No.
- The apple? - You find it cute, right?
Dong Hwi, how about one more photo?
- I'll choose the cute one. - I'll finish it here.
- One, two... - I chose the best one. Three.
I think she'll choose the one on the right this time.
Three.
(Picking)
Dong Hwi, she's smiling.
- Maybe she just likes Sung Woo. - I...
- Thank you. - You... Sung Woo.
- No cat can be a match to Siru. - Thank you.
This is what it felt like.
It's like picking who's more handsome...
between me and V with our photos.
It's like Dong Hwi...
insisting that I'm better-looking.
I understood it right away.
I have nothing to say.
That sudden silence gave me goosebumps.
That's because when BTS is on the screen,
I keep my mouth shut.
That's what I learned to do.
That makes me feel bad.
Anyway, that's how it feels.
We're leaving. Bye, kid.
Bye. Where is Heedong?
- Take care. - Bye.
Bye, guys.
Luke, don't get sick.
(Don't get sick and take care.)
Be happy.
Gosh, they're so cute.
How cute.
They're so cute.
Let's go, loser.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
I'm so happy.
I feel fully charged emotionally.
Get in, boss.
(Shall we get going for real now?)
Hello.
We're finally going to the block toy store.
You like block toys.
I'm in love with them currently.
I'm deeply in love with them.
(CODE KUNST's hobby these days is playing with block toys.)
Gosh, I have so much respect. Goodness.
(Filled with builds that he completed)
(Colorful block toy life)
I used to love block toys.
I also loved them since I was a kid.
But here's why I keep...
playing with block toys at home these days.
When I work on my music...
I'd do this and that while making music.
I felt like I became stupid.
- Oh, as in sharp thinking? - Yes.
My focus has really declined.
I thought, "This won't do."
"I should do something..."
"that will get me a result after investing a lot of my time."
So I don't really...
play with small block toys.
- Me neither. - Right.
I only play with the ones...
- that take a few days to complete. - A few days?
- He plays with difficult ones. - That's a lot like me.
But can you feel that you can focus better after playing with them?
I can totally feel that it gets better.
This is when I felt I was really pathetic.
I was watching YouTube clips on my phone.
But I left my TV on too.
I left my TV on...
and was watching something else on my phone.
I thought, "I can't focus on one thing."
That's what occurred to me.
And I found two solutions.
One was reading, and the other one was block toys.
You can't do either if you don't solely concentrate on it.
- That's true. - Because you can't move on.
You can't multitask with those.
It helped me greatly.
If you multitask while playing with block toys,
you have to disassemble them again...
- because you'd skip a step. - That's right.
- Right. - That's right.
It's the same for me. I was reading a script for a play,
and I realized my ability to memorize got a lot worse.
So I thought, "I've become mentally sluggish."
I worked even harder on the block toys that were stacked at home.
(The block toy builds that Dong Hwi made)
- That must be difficult. - They take long.
How cute.
That's made with block toys?
- Titanic. - That's incredible.
- The inside isn't the same, right? - It is.
- It's the same? - The inside is the same.
It's exactly the same...
- as the real ship. - That's right.
- It even has insides too? - That's right.
There are engines for block toy cars too.
They must have insides...
- for it to be moving. - That's right.
If the insides are empty,
then those who like block toys would never buy them.
That must be the core.
Gosh, that'd be moving.
I completed these a few days ago.
The "Home Alone" set and Diagon Alley.
- What's that? - From "Harry Potter."
(The Hogwarts Castle from "Harry Potter")
There are so many variations.
Gosh, that's an expert level.
(Recreating masterpiece scenes from a movie through block toys)
You become a creator.
Inside the "Home Alone" set,
there are rooms that were actually in the movie.
No way.
That's too hard.
(How fascinating.)
(Meanwhile, the taxi drives to a less crowded area.)
This area feels like...
where actual residents live.
There's a mecca of block toys in an area like this?
- Apparently. - How fascinating.
What? We're here?
Is it here?
I don't see it.
- I only see apartment complexes. - Thank you.
It never occurred to me...
- that it'd be there. - Have a good day.
Wait.
Dong Hwi, I'll look it up. Let's find our way there.
Hold on. Which direction is it?
It's this way.
- I feel like we're on a trip. - You're right.
When I use a map to navigate as I walk,
- it feels like I'm on a trip. - Of course.
It must be hidden away.
It's only for those who know where it is.
Exactly.
(Thinking)
Sung Woo.
We're going in the right direction, right?
Where are we?
Here? It's H Apartment in Sajik-dong.
Where is this place?
Oh, it's Sajik Elementary School.
- But it's... - It's just a residential area.
Right. There was a school.
(Sajik Elementary School)
Where is it?
(Are we going the right way?)
It's here, Dong Hwi.
- It's this building? - It's this building.
Gosh.
The block toy store is here?
It really looks like the store won't be there.
Right?
- It's here. - There's no sign.
(The block toy store is here?)
Wait. Is it that one?
That must be it.
It's the one with a yellow sign.
Where? Oh, you're right.
No way. They found it.
(A block toy store with a yellow sign at the end of the arcade)
- It's really small. - Yes, it's very small.
- What is that? - It looks like...
an unmanned ice cream shop.
- For real. - I know.
You wouldn't notice it if you walk past it.
(Relatable)
Gosh, there are block toys inside.
Let's go inside.
Hey, be careful.
You're so excited.
Gosh, look at the inside.
(Today's destination they've waited the whole day for)
- Gosh, hello, sir. - Oh, my!
Gosh.
Gosh, the inside is the treasure trove.
(The treasure trove filled with block toys)
Gosh, a block enthusiast must've opened that store.
- That's right. - Right?
Yes.
(There are even unopened new products.)
Why did he buy them if he wasn't going to assemble them?
He wants to...
- just collect them. - That's right.
Even for comic books,
if it's the first edition of "Dragon Ball,"
- you'd keep them unopened. - That's right.
- It's like that. - Oh, that's how they think.
You know the drama, "Winter Sonata?"
Yes, one with Yon-sama.
The fans have one for displaying, one solely for collection,
and one for watching.
- They have 3 sets each? - They buy 3 sets.
Those who really love block toys buy 2 or 3 sets.
- That's right. - Oh, one for keeps...
- They don't open it at all. - and one for assembling.
Gosh, they'd need a big storage.
(The block toys fill the wide shelf.)
(There are even products with set numbers in three digits.)
- What's that? - Set numbers...
indicate the order of release.
These days, the numbers go up to something like 67,000.
If it's 554,
that means it was released in the 70s or 80s.
- That must be really precious. - It's expensive.
- It was released in the early days. - Like really long ago.
That's the vintage product.
It's a really old vintage product.
My mother bought me one on the Children's Day...
when I was in elementary school.
It was an underwater exploration set called the Aqua Set.
It was a little over 100 dollars.
But now, it costs around 2,000 to 3,000 dollars.
The brand has a long history.
- This is crazy. - The block toys I've never seen.
These days,
I'm even studying block toy products.
- You're even studying them? - Yes.
Like which set has which characteristics.
You're studying them. I see.
Gosh, seriously...
(Going forward as though he's possessed)
(Amazed)
So these are the old block toy sets.
- You're right. - If you look here,
there are block toy sets released in the 70s and 80s.
The ones that say LEGOLAND.
That's even before I was born.
(The block toys started to sell in Korea in the 80s.)
Doesn't that make you excited?
(Exclaiming)
- I think I've seen it. - Right?
It brings back childhood nostalgia for everyone.
You're right.
Look. It's riding a horse.
The System sets are from the 90s.
These were released after the 2000s.
There's one from another country too.
(The products we're more familiar with)
Oh, my. I remember that.
- I remember! - The glow-in-the-dark ghost.
That's right!
I have a strong nostalgia...
for old block toys.
The ones I liked...
were monkey, octopus, and shark.
I have a great memory of those parts.
Those pieces were only released at that time,
and they're not released anymore.
But I heard this store had it, so I went all the way to Busan.
You can travel back in time with that piece alone.
- That's right. - Totally.
I bit mine a lot, so it has a lot of teeth marks.
Right! You bite it off because you assembled it wrong.
- I see. Like this? - To take the head off.
And one side would be gone.
On your left...
are bikes and Batman products.
We even have "Harry Potter" sets.
- We have The Wild West sets too. - They're the old style.
- Gold. - Gosh.
Actually...
So these are the displayed builds.
- I'm into castles these days. - Castles.
- They're legit castles. - I'm deep in love with them.
- Castles? - There are castle bases...
and marine bases on display.
Gosh, they're so cool.
Oh, there are soldiers.
Even the trees are different.
- They're old trees. Cypress trees. - I know. They're old trees.
I can tell at a glance. Such trees aren't released these days.
Every the block toy tree looked like that.
I know.
That tree is really expensive now.
Because they're not released anymore.
So some sell only the trees.
- Those trees aren't sold anymore. - Yes.
They used to be everywhere, rolling around on the floor,
at our friends' places.
They'd be under the sofa as well.
- We'd run around and step on them, - Right, when we step on them,
- and we'd scream. - it'd hurt badly.
- We'd bump our little toes into it. - Right.
We'd see it everywhere.
- And that's expensive now? - Yes.
It's crazy because people want to get the tree only.
I should've collected them from then.
- That's exactly what I'm saying. - Seriously.
- I should've collected the trees. - Seriously. They were just...
(If we just collected the trees under the sofa...)
Is this the Knights' Castle?
- Yes, it's Lion Knights' Castle. - Right. Lion Knights' Castle.
- It was recently discontinued. - That's right.
They said I should buy it...
before the price rises even if it's secondhand.
- You mean Lion Knights' Castle? - Yes.
- This one's cool. - It's cool, right?
This one's really cool.
- Yes, it's chrome. - That's crazy.
It's chrome.
(A chrome knight)
This one is really cool.
I assembled this yesterday.
Oh, really? Yesterday?
- The owner is excited. - The owner is excited.
(Curious)
It's a shark.
- A shark. - There's a shark.
This is the headquarters of a pirate base.
It's also from the 90s.
I'm getting goosebumps.
Because I love block toys so much,
I jump from time to time even when we're talking about it.
Like how we're gathered here. It's just a toy, actually.
We'd gather like this and talk about a toy.
We're like, "This is the marine base."
(Serious)
- This is... - I also thought that way.
- It is indeed awkward. - I also...
Three fully grown men would look at the plastic toy and go,
- "This is the marine base." - "This is the marine base."
- "This is..." - It's from the 90s.
He said that's the marine base.
You were so funny just now.
"There's a shark."
You said it as if...
(I can't take it easy when it comes to sharks.)
Please be careful.
- What is it? - Let me through.
I don't think he was telling me to be careful.
Oh, right.
Oh, be careful of the toys?
(How careful must we be?)
If you look inside...
(The space where there's a door lock)
Gosh, it's double protected.
There was a door lock on it too.
(In the corner of the block toy store...)
There are only rare products in there.
Really?
There are only truly rare products.
(A splendid lineup)
I'm sure there are a few that'd make you nostalgic.
(Filled with vintage block toys)
This is the most expensive one...
- in my store. - Really?
- It's 6,000 dollars. - This is 6,000 dollars?
What, 6,000 dollars?
- It's 6,000 dollars? - He said that's 6,000 dollars.
Gosh. This is...
It must have a long history.
- It does. - How so?
It's the Maersk Truck from the early days.
It's a vintage car.
That's right. It's rare.
Cars like that aren't released anymore.
There must be only a few of those...
- around the world. - There's only a few.
Its value has increased a lot now.
- That's crazy. - Six thousand dollars?
- Gosh. - This is the ultimate one.
- It's the ultimate one? - It's the third generation.
It's the pirate base.
That was popular in our days.
That's right. The block toys from our days...
- were all about pirates. - The flag.
I remember.
This is a bat castle.
- Park Ji Sung? - Yes.
A bat castle.
- Oh, I see. - Yes.
I thought it was a 2002-edition.
It was really popular in Korea too.
This one here.
Can I go inside for a second?
Sure. Got it.
(He was close to the secret room,)
(but he could only watch over their shoulders.)
- Sung Woo. - Yes?
One second. Let me see them too.
Let me see them too.
Hold on. Let me...
Gosh.
(Walking in)
(Struggling)
- Be careful of that at the back. - I should really be careful.
- Hey. - Be careful.
It's really...
(It almost fell.)
I'll just creep close to the ground.
- There are some on the bottom too. - Yes.
Gosh, Dong Hwi.
It's because of his jacket.
Oh, it's because of his jacket.
(Shaking)
- Be careful. It's okay. - Yes.
What do you mean by, "Be careful. It's okay?"
(What does he actually mean?)
- What am I supposed to do? - I...
(Be careful.)
- This is another one. - It's the glow-in-the-dark ghost.
It's a castle battle set.
I didn't expect to see the glow-in-the-dark ghost here.
- A shark. - There's a shark here too.
There's a shark here!
It's a monkey.
A monkey and a parrot.
- A monkey... - There's a gold coin too.
As if he was seeing one for the first time at his age.
- "It's a monkey!" - Dong Hwi, it's a monkey.
- A monkey. - It's kind of creepy, though.
The monkey is like a human.
- Oh, I remember that monkey. - Right? You remember, right?
- Totally. - There's only one of that.
- It's a true treasure. - We have only one of that.
The one who touched it the most should buy it.
- Well... - The one who touched it the most?
- I think you should get this. - You can put it down.
But I really want that monkey.
- Right? This many monkeys. - Yes. The monkey and...
- You should get a monkey. - Monkeys...
- It has a monkey. - A monkey.
It has one.
- Right. I even remember its tail. - You remember, right?
- It's to my liking. - No way.
This one also has monkeys.
There's a shark too.
- The monkey is holding a gun. - Yes.
- A gun? - What?
No way.
I think I remember that too.
There's a monkey in it.
Rescue the monkey.
I should get this.
- This... - Why are you so keen about monkeys?
- Why do you like them so much? - It's like this.
They release monkeys these days too.
But they're different, right?
- But it's too sophisticated. - Right.
- It's too detailed. - That's right.
It's too similar to a real one.
I really wanted that one too.
I mean... Dong Hwi, the monkey...
- It has a banana too. - There's a banana too.
It has a banana too.
I'll take these for now.
I even remember the banana too.
- Right? You remember, right? - Incredible.
What should I get?
Over here.
(Thinking)
(Looking around)
It looks like he's there to steal.
- A thief? - I bet he put a few sharks...
in his pocket.
(Quietly scanning in a suspicious-looking outfit)
Hold on. Gosh, this...
You can get ready for this year's Christmas in advance.
- I didn't know they had this. - Right.
I don't have any Christmas decorations at home.
I don't even have a tree.
My house doesn't have any Christmas vibe on Christmas.
I think this is better.
Right. I should assemble this.
I think I'll be able to marry if I buy this.
- Gosh. - I'll get you one.
Let's get one each and get married.
- It's the wedding series. - Yes.
The act of coming here itself drifts us away from marriage.
That's true.
- I'll get it for you as a gift. - I'm being honest.
- I'll get it for you as a gift. - Really?
- I'll take these. - Great.
- Gosh. - This one's cool.
- Let's take this. - Goodness.
- It's really cool. - Is it Batmobile?
Batmobile.
- I'll take this too. - All right.
- This and... - He's getting a lot.
Five in total.
It's perfect.
- Thank you, sir. - Thank you.
- Gosh. - I'll assemble them well.
I'd love to shake your hand, but mine are full.
You must be a bit embarrassed.
Dong Hwi.
Let's go separately when we go home.
(Chuckling)
I'm so embarrassed. Let's go separately.
Gosh, this is...
Sung Woo, can't you slow down?
(Building Friendship Block by Block)
(Next story)
(Rainbow Running Horses Special, Part 4)
Hello.
(It's been 2 years since she started living alone.)
(Tsuki)
(Fancam with 15 million views)
(She drew attention as the master of expressions.)
(She completed a marathon recently despite her injury.)
(She proved she has a tenacious spirit.)
(A passionate singer with no limits, Tsuki)
(Tsuki's house is black.)
(I feel comfortable when it's dark.)
(It'd have been nice if the wallpaper was black too.)
(Power walking in all black?)
(Devotion?)
(Laid-off?)
(Axe-chopping?)
(Studying Korean early in the morning)
(She's been living in Korea...)
(for 10 years.)
(Call me Kim Tsuki.)
Okay. Let's hurry up.
(Lunch menu)
(Braised kimchi)
(Thank you for the food.)
(Arrived at the supermarket cheerfully in an all-black outfit)
(Cheerfully asking questions)
(- Bollack? - Pollack.)
(Salted pollack roe...)
(Is it salty?)
(Where are thin pork belly slices?)
(Her Korean is improving today as well.)
(Laughing)
(One)
(She's talking with someone on the phone?)
(- Six. - Six?)
(Tsuki's parents)
(Mom and Dad, try speaking in Korean.)
(It's okay!)
(Thank you!)
(My hair is like that of Park Sae Ro Yi.)
(Always Growing, Today and Tomorrow)
(Breathing out)
(Martial Artist Ju Seung is training hard from early afternoon?)
(I've gotten into fashion recently.)
(I should get rid of old clothes to become a fashionista.)
(That's why he went to secondhand clothing sharing shop.)
(He sent a total of 65 pieces of clothing to donate.)
(With light steps, he headed to...)
(A vintage shop, a must-visit place for fashionistas)
(And someone who'll help with his big transition)
(Ju Seung's closest actor friend)
(Actor Son Woo Hyeon who is famous for his boyfriend photos)
Let's go for a young style.
Shall we try a street and hip style?
(But...)
(the pants...)
(This is sagging.)
(Fashionista power)
(The lower the pants,)
(the more complete it is.)
(Falling)
(Embarrassed)
(That's right.)
(There was a style I wanted to follow.)
(Some people call me JUHOON.)
(Some told me I look like...)
(JUHOON of CORTIS.)
(This is it!)
(I look like an idol?)
(Ju Star's Fashion)